(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T13:26:03.904355",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
I went to karaoke recently.
なんかさ、2時間で解散と思うじゃん、そっからなのよ。
You'd think we'd split up after two hours, but that's when it starts.
いろんなことできるわけ！やばいぞ、うまい！
You can do so many things! It's amazing, and so good!
JOYSOUND X PARK
X PARK最高！
X PARK is the best!
JOYSOUND X1
本日は宝鐘マリン1stライブ「Ahoy! 君たちみんなパイレーツにご来場いただきまして誠にありがとうございます。」
Thank you very much for attending Houshou Marine's 1st Live, 'Ahoy! All You Pirates!'
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意並びにご案内を申し上げます。
Before the start of the performance, we have some important notes and announcements for our audience.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of filming, recording, or video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮下さいますようお願い申し上げます。
The venue is non-smoking. We ask that you refrain from smoking.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合は無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
If you feel unwell at any time, please do not push yourself and notify a staff member.
あーい！宝鐘ライブ参戦して宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンでーす！
Ahoy! I'm Houshou Marine, captain of the Houshou Pirates, participating in Houshou Live!
ちょっと長いけどキミたちまだ注意事項があるからちゃんと聞くんだぞ！
It's a bit long, but you guys still have some safety instructions left, so listen up properly!
会場内でのもしライブ中ダイブ、肩車、ステージ上に物を投げ込む、
If you dive, put someone on your shoulders, or throw objects onto the stage during the live...
ステージ上に上がる、強引に通路を塞ぐ、前に押し寄せる、
Go onto the stage, forcibly block aisles, surge forward,
周りのお客さまのご迷惑となるような不自然なコール、奇声！絶対にしないってマリンとの約束だぞ！
or make unnatural calls or screams that bother other guests—that's a promise to Marine, absolutely no doing that!
あと、公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為、不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、腕を振り回す、上半身をそらすなどの過激な応援行為、
Also, excessive cheering such as making loud noises that disrupt the performance, violently swinging hands or arms at unnatural times, or bending the upper body backward,
過度なジャンプ行為など他のイチミの皆に迷惑がかかる危険行為は一切禁止です！
and dangerous acts like excessive jumping that trouble other crew members are strictly prohibited!
(ちょ、見せばい！)
(Hey, show it!)
(え、ちょっとやめなさい！ちょっとマリンのクソみたいなものやめてください！本物のマリンが続きを読みます！)
(Hey, stop that! Please stop making Marine-like crap! The real Marine will read the rest!)
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入っているぞ、キミたち！
This performance has video streaming and photo shooting cameras inside the venue, you guys!
客席のお客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます、キミたち映っちゃうよ、うん。
The audience's reactions might be captured on camera, you guys will be on screen, yep.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますのであらかじめご了承ください！
Please understand in advance that these videos and photos may be used for promotions and such!
(お前も偽物じゃねえか！)
(You're a fake too!)
(そんなことないよ！違うよ！)
(That's not true! No way!)
準備は、せーの！それでは間もなく開演いたします！
Ready, one, two! The performance will begin shortly!
お席に付いておまちください！
Please take your seats and wait!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge ?
Did your pulse race by the rouge?
出航ー！！
To set sail!
無罪！無罪！美女無罪！
No guilt, no guilt! The queen of beauty not guilty!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine, marine! Marine is not guilty!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
So bright-bright, tide so-much-much!
ねぇ、言ったよね？
Hey, didn't you say it?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age is nothing more than a number
そういうめんどくさいのも
Then will you look past all those explosive mines,
含めて愛してくれるって
and love me unconditionally?
ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？ 言ってない？
Hey, hey, didn't you say it, didn't you?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Huh, so you're going to act that way
ちなみにこの船では
Ah, and just so you know, in this ship
美女無罪が適用されますけど？
Beautiful girls are free of guilt
まかせて！ 魔法で若返り
I got it, magic will make me young again!
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ
And I'll show you, my hidden colors only to you
トクベツですよ～？
Because you're special!
あぁ… アタシ厄介よ
(Ah) I'll be a mess
あぁ… 港なんじゃない
(Ah) No port manages to excite me
はしゃいじゃないわ 近頃はね
Recently, I've been feeling
宝の島にしてほしい気分
That it must be the power of a treasure island!
出航ー！！
To set sail!
キュートは正義 美女無罪
Cuteness makes right, this beautiful girl is not guilty
キミの一番 目指してヨーソロ！
Aiming to be your #1, stand firm!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
I lack confidence, but I'll do my best to achieve it!
ahoy！！
Ahoy!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyu run,
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるるんるん
Kyu kyu kyururun
恋する気持ち 17歳
So in love, sweet 17
0時になっちゃう オトナの時間
The clock will strike midnight, class M time!
やっぱりキラキラ もっとクラクラ
So bright-bright, tide so-much-much!
ド・キ・ド・キ・し・て rouge ?
Did your pulse race by the rouge?
まだ早い♡
Not yet, it's too early
だだだ、だめですか？
Is i-i-is this wrong?
フリルのお洋服着たら
If I wear a ruffled dress
そんなこと、ないよ
No, it's fine
だだだ、だだって
D-d-but...
魔法少女になってみたい
I want to be a magical girl!
ギリギリ有罪！？
Guilty, guilty? Just a little!
進路はなんざんす星
The path is decided that it will be by the southwest!
ちょっと足んない積極性？
Lack initiative, crew?
結局キミももっと若い子？
Do you prefer younger girls too?
なんだってするから見捨てないでキミたち！
I'll do anything, so please, don't leave me crew!
ちょっとイイトコ見せてみたい！
I want to see you at your best
あぁ… たまにいじけちゃう
(Ah) Sometimes I get discouraged
あぁ… それでもいいの？
(Ah) Is that okay?
年齢だもん本気にしちゃう
I'm at that age, so I gotta take it seriously
アホイ！
Ahoy!
まだだよ パッション
Not yet, passion!
想いを解き放て
Unleash your feelings!
赤く
Red and...
きらめくパッション
...sparkling passion!
10秒前
10 seconds before,
走れ ガチ恋列車
run, gachikoi train!
日焼けも出るわ
Getting sunburned too,
ギラギラ
glittering brightly!
沈黙汗もしたたる女だけど
A woman dripping with sweat in silence, but...
あ、船長？
Ah, Captain?
船長はセンシティブだとバンされちゃうのですね！
If the Captain is too sensitive, she'll get banned!
はにゃ～！
Hanyaa!
歌われてから
After being sung,
漕ぎ戻せ それが本章
paddle back, that's the true chapter.
酷毒な
With you merciless,
君たちとなら辿り着ける
cruel people, I can reach it.
逆境中のエールさぁと
An eager cheer amidst adversity,
夜空のしけや歌おうよ
let's sing through the stormy night!
足りない
It's not enough,
この景色
this scenery!
大切なんだただよ
It's just so precious...
歌げだ 歌げだ 騒げや 騒げ
Sing, sing! Make noise, make noise!
踊る阿呆に 見る阿呆
Fools who dance, fools who watch!
同じ阿呆なら 踊らにゃ損々
Since we're all fools, you might as well dance!
逆さになる片手に 意気地なし よさこい
With one hand upside down, cowardly yosakoi!
あほい あほい あほい
Ahoy, ahoy, ahoy!
お留守番よろしく
Take care of the house while I'm away,
世界で一番
the best in the world!
けすがき 消すがき
Erase it, erase it!
エロがき エロがき
Perverted brat, perverted brat!
パンツ没収しゃーん！
Confiscate your panties, ta-da!
女から 男から
From women, from men!
戻り 戻り 喉はスクール
Return, return, throats are parched!
船長のちょっといいとこ見てみたい
I want to see a cool side of the Captain!
もっと！ もっと！ うふふふ！
More! More! Ufufu!
キャッチーに やれファイティング
Catchy, do some fighting!
ズッ友の お・ん・な・の・こ
Girls who are best friends forever!
燃え燃えきゅん 出会ってゴリ押しで
Burning moe kyun, bulldozing right from meeting!
あ、もう！船長は君たちをそんな骨まで育てた覚えはありません！本当にね、滅多だぞ？
Ah, jeez! The Captain doesn't remember raising you guys to be such boneheads! Seriously, how rare is that?
立てば地獄 座れば地獄 歩く姿はセンシティブ
Stand, it's hell; sit, it's hell; walking, it's sensitive.
夢を見よう この船で 後悔なんて賛成しない
Let's dream on this ship, I won't agree to any regrets!
君たちの おかげで私は 船長みだれるから
Thanks to you guys, the Captain is going wild!
ひらけ船長から 打て！
Open up, from the Captain, strike!
時計を上げて さぁ 出発だ 我ら宝条
Wind the clock, now set off, we are Houshou!
海賊団 悶絶片手に旗を上げ この海をジャックしちゃおう
Pirate crew, with agony in one hand raise the flag, let's jack this sea!
よそ見していておいでよ 共にしよう よそ見もあぁ 最初の君に
Look away and come along, let's share it, looking away too, ah, to you first.
夜はことさら 曲がれ胸 この海峡の解読だぁ
The night is all the more twisted in the chest, deciphering this strait!
さぁ よそ見していておいでよ 解読だぁ！
Now, look away and come along, decipher it!
それではいきますよ 瞬間！キャリナ！
Here we go! Instantly, carina!
ケアリナ 行きますよ！
Carina, here we go!
ねえ、いてよねえ 全然なんて関係ないってさ そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
Hey, stay with me, hey. It doesn't matter at all, loving even the troublesome parts of me.
ねえねえ いてよねえ 行ってない？ ふん、そう言うこと言うんだ。ちなみにこの船では微少女無罪が適用されますけど？
Hey hey, stay with me, hey. Didn't you go? Hmph, you say that. By the way, on this ship, the "cute girl innocence" applies, you know?
讓らせて 魔法で若返る
Let me rejuvenate with magic!
秘密のすらは君だけ 特別ですよ あたしだってよ
The secret slant is just for you, it's special, even I am...
港となんかじゃ はしゃがないわ 近付くまで
I won't get excited at just any port until we get close.
宝の島にしてほしいの
I want you to make it a treasure island!
銃から響くしゃばちゃむたい
Echoing from the gun, noisy and clumsy,
君の一番で出社したい
I want to report to work as your number one!
夜空 本当は自信ないけど 頑張っちゃう
In the night sky, actually I'm not confident, but I'll do my best!
うんうんうん 君は今気付づく なんだい？全裸になっちゃうわ 大人の時間
Uh-huh, you're realizing it now, what is it? I'll end up completely naked, adult time!
ドキドキして 無視 まだ早い
My heart is racing, ignoring it, it's still too early.
まだだよ みてたぞ たてばじょ...
Not yet, I was watching, standing is jo...
だめですか フリルの服から そんなことないよ
Is it no good? From the ruffled dress, no way!
だってだって魔法少女になってみたい
Because, because I want to become a magical girl!
心臓にチャーム 美少女無罪
Charm on the heart, innocent beautiful girl
あれあれどうしたの？
My, my, what's wrong?
めんどくさいかなんて言っちゃって
Saying things like "Is it troublesome?"
かまってくれるキミが好き
I love the you who pays attention to me.
AHOY!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu, kyu, kyurun,
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
kyu, kyu, kyurunrun.
優しくしてね 17歳
Be gentle to me, 17 years old.
──“罪な女”ね？
--"A sinful woman," huh?
出航──！！
Set sail--!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent beautiful girl.
キミの一番目指して ヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro!
冗談も大好き だけど真剣よ
I love jokes too, but I'm serious.
AHOY!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu, kyu, kyurun,
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
kyu, kyu, kyurunrun.
恋する気持ち 17歳
Feelings of love, 17 years old.
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
Reaching midnight, adult time.
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Sparkling, even more dizzying,
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge？
heart-pounding rouge?
まだ早い
Still too early.
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!
マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Sparkling, even more dizzying,
“マリン”じゃなくて“マリン船長”だろうん！？
Isn't it "Captain Marine" instead of just "Marine"!?
心臓にチャーム 美少女無罪
Charm on the heart, innocent beautiful girl.
あれあれどうしたの？
My, my, what's wrong?
めんどくさいかなんて言っちゃって
Saying things like "Is it troublesome?"
かまってくれるキミが好き
I love the you who pays attention to me.
AHOY!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu, kyu, kyurun,
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
kyu, kyu, kyurunrun.
優しくしてね 17歳
Be gentle to me, 17 years old.
──“罪な女”ね？
--"A sinful woman," huh?
出航──！！
Set sail--!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent beautiful girl.
キミの一番目指して ヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro!
冗談も大好き だけど真剣よ
I love jokes too, but I'm serious.
AHOY!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu, kyu, kyurun,
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
kyu, kyu, kyurunrun.
恋する気持ち 17歳
Feelings of love, 17 years old.
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
Reaching midnight, adult time.
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Sparkling, even more dizzying,
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge？
heart-pounding rouge?
まだ早い
Still too early.
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocent!
マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱ キラキラ もっと クラクラ
Sparkling, even more dizzying,
“マリン”じゃなくて“マリン船長”だろうん！？
Isn't it "Captain Marine" instead of just "Marine"!?
心臓にチャーム
Charm on the heart,
美少女無罪
innocent beautiful girl.
まだ早い
Still too early.
美少女無罪！
Innocent beautiful girl!
マリンじゃなくて
Not Marine,
マリン船長だろ
it's Captain Marine!
Ahoy!! 宝鐘マリン1st LIVE 君たちみんなパイレーツ♡
[Title: Ahoy!! Houshou Marine 1st LIVE - Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡]
予測されない 舵のように
Like an unpredictable helm,
私のフェチが めくれるたびに
every time my fetish is flipped open,
掘り出されて しまうのかしら
I wonder if it gets dug up.
それが知りたくて
Wanting to know that
とても
so much.
掘り出されて しまうのかしら
I wonder if it gets dug up.
島主の頭
The island owner's head,
それが知したくて とても
wanting to know that so much.
あなたの瞳の奥に
Deep in your eyes,
旅していく
traveling onward,
私のセンチメンタルジャーニー
my sentimental journey.
つぼみの名前で 夢を見ていたい
Wanting to dream under the name of a bud,
劇のように美しい 物語だけ見てたいわ
I only want to watch a story as beautiful as a play.
マリンはまだ17だから
Because Marine is still 17.
夢を見ていたい
Wanting to dream,
劇のように美しい 物語だけ見てたいわ
I only want to watch a story as beautiful as a play.
マリンはまだ17だから
Because Marine is still 17.
何かに傷ついて あなたにさらわれて
Hurt by something, carried away by you,
センチメンタルジャーニー
Sentimental Journey.
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Not guilty! Not guilty! Pretty girl not guilty!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is not guilty!
やっぱり キラキラ もっと クラクラ
After all, it's glittering, getting even more dizzy
ねえ、言ったよね？
Hey, you told me so, right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter at all
そういうめんどうくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
That you'd love me even with all those troubles
ねえねえ、言ったよね？ 言ってない？
Hey hey, you told me so? You didn't?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hmm, is that what you're gonna say?
ちなみに この 船 では
By the way, on this ship,
美少女無罪 が 適用 されます けど？
the "Pretty Girl Not Guilty" defense applies, right?
まかせ て ！ 魔法 で 若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic
ヒミツ の 素顔 は キミ に だけ
My secret bare face is just for you
トクベツ です ～ ？！
Is it special~?
あぁ... アタシ 厄介 よ ね
Ah... I'm a handful, you know
港 なんか じゃ はしゃいじゃ ない わ 最近 は ね
Lately, I don't just get excited at the port
宝 の 島 に して ほしい 気分
I'm in the mood to make it an island of treasure
出航 ーー ！！
Set sail!!
キュート は 正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, pretty girl not guilty
キミ の 一番 目指して ヨーソロー ！
Aiming to be your number one, ahoy!
本当は 自信 ない けど 頑張っちゃう
Actually I'm not confident, but I'll do my best
ahoy ！！
Ahoy!!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん
Kyu kyu kyurun
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurunrun
恋する 気持ち 17歳
A heart in love, 17 years old
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's turning midnight, adult time
やっぱり キラキラ もっと クラクラ
After all, it's glittering, getting even more dizzy
ド・キ・ド・キ・し て rouge ？
Thump-thump-thump, feeling rouge?
まだ 早い ♡
Still too early ♡
だっ だっ だめ です か ？！
D-d-is it no good?!
フリル の 服装 着たら
If I wear frilly clothes
そんな こと 、 ない よ
"There's no such thing"
だっ だっ だって ば
B-b-but
魔法少女 に なって みたい
I want to try becoming a magical girl
ギリギリ 有罪 ！ ？
Barely guilty!?
進路 は なん な ん 星
Our course is the what-what star?
ちょっぴり 足ん ない 積極性 ？！
A little lacking in proactivity?!
結局 キミ も もっと 若い 子 ？！
In the end, do you prefer younger girls too?!
なん だって する から
I'll do anything, so
見捨て ない で 、 キミ たち ！
Don't abandon me, you guys!
出航 ーー ！！
Set sail!!
さあ、始まりましたー！
Now then, it has begun!
盛り上がっております！キミパイ火曜祭、司会の狼ミオと
Things are getting heated! Tuesday's Kimipai Festival, hosted by Ookami Mio and
白銀ノエルと！皆さんお待たせしました！
Shirogane Noel. Everyone, thanks for waiting!
いや、お待たせしすぎたのかもしれません。いつもの通りの白上フブキです。
Well, maybe you've waited too long. It's Fubuki Shirakami as usual.
そして！本日の主演の！
And! Today's starring...
あはーい！ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンでーす！
Ahai! Houshou Marine, captain of the Houshou Pirate Crew from Hololive 3rd Gen!
よっ！キミたぴー！
Yo! Kimitapi!
なんかさっき影ナレの偽物のマリン、本物のマリンだと思った人？
Say, how many of you thought the fake Marine in the opening announcement was the real Marine?
えっ？嘘！そんなの言ったんですか？
Eh? No way! Did she say that?
嘘！偽物なんていたんですか？
No way! There was a fake?
偽物いらっしゃったんですか？嘘だよね？
A fake was here? You're lying, right?
私たちの知らないところで、勝手に偽物がいたって。
Without us knowing, some fake was just running around.
いてねえだろ全然！怖いですね。黙られんなよ！
No way there was! Not at all! Scary. Shut up!
恐ろしいことがいらっしゃいますね。そうですね。そうですね。はい。
That's quite a scary thing. Indeed. Indeed. Yes.
はい、ついに始まりましたけども火曜祭。そうなんですもう、ドキドキで、キミたちもみんなに、みんなにみんなに、あーみんなみんなみんなみんな！
Yes, it has finally begun, Tuesday's Festival. That's right, my heart is pounding, and you guys too, everyone, everyone, ah everyone everyone!
あー君たち君たち君たち君たち...私たちもね、君たち君たち君たち！
Ah you guys you guys... Us too, you guys you guys!
みなさんどうも、どうもみなさん。いや、すごいですね、今日もね。こんなにたくさんの客さんがいらっしゃって。
Hello everyone, hello. Wow, it's amazing today too. With so many guests/audience members here.
すいませんマリン、一つ気になったんですけど。
Sorry Marine, one thing was bothering me.
なんですか？あの、マリンが、あの、た、た、例えば、その、「座れ、座れ」ば
What is it? Um, Marine, for example, if you 'sit, sit down'
みんな言っ、あのありました、ありましたね。そういえば、その時なんか誰か「マリンは撮れよ」って言ってました？確かに聞こえましたね。「マリンは撮れよ」って聞こえた気がしたんですけど。
Everyone said—ah, there was, there was. Come on, did someone say 'Film Marine!' back then? I definitely heard it. I felt like I heard 'Film Marine!'.
言った方ちょっとサイリウム振ってみてください。
Whoever said that, please wave your penlights.
あそこですね！
Right over there!
あの、いちみでですね、見つけた。
Um, in Ichimi, I found them.
あの、いちみでございますね。どんだけ声でけえ、一人で、一人で聞こえてきた。すごい。
Ah, it's Ichimi. How loud can one person be, heard it all by herself. Amazing.
はい、すごいですね。あ、ちょっとね、ちゃんとね、見えてますよ、今。すごい。あのね、一旦まず、すごいね、前にね、あの、くま、くまの格好...
Yes, it's amazing. Ah, sort of, I can see you clearly right now. Amazing. Um, first of all, way upfront, um, bear, bear costume...
可愛い女がいます！可愛い女！ちょっと、歓声がね、特大歓声が今来ております。
There's a cute girl! A cute girl! Wow, huge cheers are coming in right now.
あ、みんな可愛いっすよ。隣の、隣の男も可愛い。隣の男！
Ah, everyone's cute. The guy next to them is also cute. The guy next door!
上の男たち、上の女たち！いや、すごいですね、みんな可愛い！
The guys up top, the girls up top! Man, that's amazing, everyone's cute!
配信の皆さんもいらっしゃいますのでね。コメントのきみたち可愛いよー！
The streaming audience is here too. Comment section you guys are so cute!
コメントのきみたちもね、ちゃんとね、ちゃんと見てますから、安心してくださいね。適宜、適宜ね、拾わさせていただきますから。はいはい。俺ら可愛いのか？とのお言葉です。可愛いと思いますよ。
You guys in the comments too, I'm watching you properly, so don't worry. I'll pick up on things appropriately. Yes yes. Are we cute? That's what you're saying. I think you're cute.
まあ、これからね、まあ、始まったばかりなんですけれども！
Well, from here on, well, it has only just begun!
まだまだね、たくさんゲストが...そうですね、いらっしゃいますね。
There are still plenty of guests... That's right, there are.
なんですけど、たくさん呼んじゃいました、ソロライブとはいったいって感じでいっぱいいっぱい呼んじゃいました。いや、素晴らしいです。
Even so, I invited so many, it feels like 'what happened to my solo live', I invited so many. It's wonderful.
まあ、昭和火曜祭、いつもね、ゲストの方たくさんいらっしゃいますからね。そうなんです。とても楽しみでございます。はい。
Well, Showa Tuesday Festival always has lots of guests, right? That's right. I'm very much looking forward to it. Yes.
ということでね、もうここからの春舞台。もう絶対見逃す時には行かないじゃないですか。もちろんですね。
So, from here on, the spring stage. You definitely wouldn't want to miss it when it comes. Of course.
ということで、会場の皆さんはもちろんなんですけど、配信チケットは概要欄から飛びますので、お見逃しなく！よろしくお願いしまーす！
So, of course for everyone at the venue, streaming tickets are available via the description, so don't miss it! Please look forward to it!
なんとね、あの、非常にインスパイアなんですけど。お、お、白身スパーズもね。
And apparently, um, they're extremely sleepy. Shiramy Spurs too.
おや？
Huh?
もしかしてこれでここまでなんですか？
Wait, is this really as far as it goes?
ここまでですか？
That's it?
えー！？
What?!
君たちもっと言ったって！
You guys should've said more!
そうだよね！
Right?
えーだよね！
Right?!
今、無料ちらみせを見ている皆さん、
Everyone watching the free preview right now...
これが、そう、そういです。
this is, well... that's it.
ええです。
Yeah.
ええということね。
That's how it is.
はい、ええちらみせで満足できないと思うので是非、
Yeah, I'm sure you won't be satisfied with just a peek, so please...
よろしくお願いしますね。
we'd appreciate your support!
お願いいたします！
Please look forward to it!
はい、ではマリンさんの先ほどのセンチメートルジャーニーなんですけども、
Right, so Marine-san, about your "Centimeter Journey" just now...
なんか替え歌なさってましたね？
it seemed like you changed the lyrics?
え？あ、そうなんです。マリンはまだ、何でしたっけ？
Huh? Ah, yeah. Marine is still... what was it?
17だから、ですね。
17 years old, right?
ケーアリーナに来ても詐欺は良くないです。
Even if we're at K-Arena, scamming isn't good.
え？
Eh?
良くないですよね、皆さん。
It's not good, right everyone?
詐欺だったんですか？
Was it a scam?
そうです。ねえ、年サバは良くないと思います。ケーアリーナまでです。
Yeah. You shouldn't lie about your age, even at K-Arena.
なんか偽物がいたり詐欺ってたりちょっと大丈夫ですか？
Um, with imposters and scammers around, are you okay?
いやいやいやいや、それが詐欺じゃなく、君たち？
No, no, no, that's not a scam! You guys?
マリンは何歳せいの？
How old is Marine?
みそじ……いやだから、結構バラバラですね。
Thirty... I mean, you guys are all over the place.
結構バラバラだけど、一味統率したほうがいいんじゃないですか？
You're all over the place, maybe you should get your crew in order?
待って、じゃあちょっと、待って待って、今17歳って言った人ー！
Wait, hold on a second! Who just said 17 years old?!
はーい！いーねー、やれよ。
Yay! Nice, go for it.
みそじって言った人ー！
Who said thirty?!
おい！やれよー！
Hey! Come on!
圧倒的に多いですねー。
That's an overwhelming majority!
いや、いいです、盛り上がってまいりましたけども。
Well, anyway, things are really heating up.
さあ、話も盛り上がってきたところではありますが、そろそろね次の曲の準備をいたしましょうか。
Now, as lively as our chat has gotten, it's almost time to get ready for the next song.
あ、そうでした、そうです。まだまだ曲いっぱいありますからね、君たち！楽しみですね。
Ah, that's right! We still have tons of songs left, everyone! Look forward to it!
それでは、次の曲まいりましょう！どうぞ！
Now then, let's move on to the next song! Here we go!